For the solution within forecast fragment, we
implemented FetchWeather/task, which extends AsyncTask. The generics
we use are just Void, and this is fine for now. Then within the doInBackground
method, we copied our networking codes snippet,
here. It's the same, except [INAUDIBLE] in
certain cases we return null instead of
setting the forecast JSON string to be null.
Previously, the code was an on create view, which expected us
inflate and return a view. So it's important that it got
to the rest of the code. Even if there was an
error in the networking code. Now that the networking code is in
a sync task, there's really nothing that comes after this in
the given background method. So it's fine to just bail early
whenever there's an error. Also know that for our log messages,
we've defined a log tag constant. At the top of this task.
This log tag is defined to be the name of the FetchWeatherTask.class. The
reason we use this syntax instead
of declaring a string FetchWeatherTask, it because
we want these two to be in sync. If you ever rename the
class then it will throw an exception unless you also update it here.